<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English on Homepage Zhuo Liu</title><link>https://joeliuz6.github.io/tags/english/</link><description>Recent content in English on Homepage Zhuo Liu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:37:57 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joeliuz6.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Testing</title><link>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 13:37:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/2021/01/07/second-post/</guid><description>See the source code of this page if you are interested.
List Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Table Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water1 Water Water Water Water Quotes What I cannot create, I do not understand2.</description></item><item><title>The Road Not Taken</title><link>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/1915/01/01/road-not-taken/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1915 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/1915/01/01/road-not-taken/</guid><description>Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both
And be one traveler, long I stood
And looked down one as far as I could
To where it bent in the undergrowth;
Then took the other, as just as fair,
And having perhaps the better claim,
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;
Though as for that the passing there
Had worn them really about the same,</description></item><item><title>Towards Flexible Fairness-accuracy Tradeoff With Label Constraints</title><link>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/1/01/01/fairness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://joeliuz6.github.io/en/1/01/01/fairness/</guid><description>Introduction: What&amp;rsquo;s fairness? The concept &amp;ldquo;fairness&amp;rdquo; was first proposed in about late 2000s, attracting a wide interest together with ethical AI in the last decade. In general, fairness can be divided into three categories: group fairness, individual fairness and conterfactual fairness, where the former two are statistical dependence measures and the latter is rooted in causal inference. So how do we define fairness?
Values of fairness in real-world applications Fairness-Accuracy tradeoff Regularization and inference with label constraints Regularization with label constraints On-training approach: Inference-based training Learning plus inference Achieve flexible fairness-accuracy tradeoff at test time Learning with constraints YOTO YODO Inference with constraints References You Only Train Once: Loss-Conditional Training of Deep Networks Dataset Fairness: Achievable Fairness On Your Data With Utility Guarantees On Regularization and Inference with Label Constraints Men Also Like Shopping:Reducing Gender Bias Amplification using Corpus-level Constraints</description></item></channel></rss>